Guide to the Albrecht Goetze Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Inventory, 1923-1971; 8.25; (22 boxes)
  - Hubbell, Harry M., 1938 (Box 9, Folder 228)
  - Huffmann, Gunter J., 1946-1953 (Box 9, Folder 228)
  - Hulin, Peter, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 228)
  - Huntington, Ellsworth, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 229)
  - Hurewitz, Jay C., 1961 (Box 9, Folder 229)
  - Hussey, Mary I.(*), 1943-1947 (Box 9, Folder 229)
  - Hussey, Mary I., 1949-1953 (Box 9, Folder 230)
  - Hyatt, James Philip, 1935-1936 (Box 9, Folder 231)
  - Hyatt, James Philip(*), 1937-1940, 1946, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 232-233)
  - Ilberg, Joannes, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 234)
  - Illinois, University of, Museum, 1950, 1953, 1967-1970 (Box 9, Folder 234)
  - Indogermanischen GeselIschaft, undated (Box 9, Folder 235)
  - Indogernmanisches Institut, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 235)
  - Ingholt, Harald(*), 1934-1942, 1953-1959 (Box 9, Folder 235)
  - Innes, T. Crispie, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 236)
  - Instituttet for Sammenlignende Kulturforskning, 1945, 1947, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 236)
  - International Commission for a Scientific and Cultural History of Mankind, 1952-1953 (Box 9, Folder 236)
  - International Committee for Assistance to Professionals, Artists and Scholars
  - International Congress of Orientalists
    See: box 10, folder 239-247
  - International Council for Philosophy and Humanistic Studies: "Requests for Subventions" and "Constitution and Composition of Member Organizations", 1959 September (Box 10, Folder 237)
  - International Council for Philosophy and Humanistic Studies: "Summary Record", 1959 September (Box 10, Folder 238)
  - International Council for Philosophy and Humanistic Studies (Box 10, Folder 238)
    See also: box 4, folder 104 See also: box 10, folder 239-247
  - International General Electric Company
  - International Research Institute, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 238)
  - International Union of Orientalists(*), 1936, 1951-1962 September, 1963 October-1964 Aug, 1964 September-1965 March-Dec, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 239-247)
  - International Union of Orientalists(*), 1967, 1969, undated (Box 10, Folder 248)
    See also: box 3, folder 63 See also: box 8, folder 183
  - International Who's Who, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 249)
  - The Interpreter's Dictionary of the Bible, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 249)
  - Iraq, Directorate General of Antiquities(*), 1946-1961, 1967, undated (Box 11, Folder 250)
    See also: box 2, folder 28-50 See also: box 9, folder 235
  - Iraq Museum
    See: box 11, folder 250
  - Isis, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 250)
  - Israel, Embassy of, Washington, D.C., 1964 (Box 11, Folder 250)
  - Israel, Ministry of Education and Culture, Department of Antiquities, 1953, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 251)
    See also: box 13, folder 320 See also: box 16, folder 402
  - Israel Exploration Journal, 1953-1955 (Box 11, Folder 251)
  - Isserlin, B.S.J., 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 251)
  - Istanbul, Arkeoloji Müzeleri, 1949-1953 (Box 11, Folder 251)
  - Izard, Jean, undated (Box 11, Folder 252)
  - Jabbar, Najim A., 1962 (Box 11, Folder 252)
  - Jack, James William, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 252)
  - Jacobsen, Thorkild(*), 1936-1945 (Box 11, Folder 252)
  - Jacobsen, Thorkild(*), 1946-1947 Jan, 1947 July-1954 (Box 11, Folder 253-255)
  - Jacobsen, Thorkild, 1955-1970 (Box 11, Folder 256)
  - Jacobsohn, Hanna, 1936-1938 (Box 11, Folder 257)
  - Jacobsohn, Helmuth, 1937-1940 (Box 11, Folder 257)
  - Jacobsohn, Hermann, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 257)
    See also: box 12, folder 310
  - Jacobson, Anna, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 257)
  - Jacobsthal, Paul(*), 1933-1937 (Box 11, Folder 258-259)
  - Jacobsthal, Paul, 1938-1939, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 260)
  - Jaeger, Werner, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 260)
  - Jameson, Michael H., 1957, 1966, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 260)
  - Jansen, Herman Ludin, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 261)
  - Jaritz, Kurt, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 261)
  - Jaspers, Carl, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 261)
  - Jastrow, Elisabeth, 1934, 1947, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 261)
  - Jastrow, Ignaz, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 261)
  - Jean, Charles-F., 1946-1947 (Box 11, Folder 261)
  - Jeffery, Arthur, 1948, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 262)
  - Jensen, Peter(*), 1924-1936 (Box 11, Folder 262)
  - Jeremias, Alfred, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 263)
  - Jeremias, Jörg, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 263)
  - Jestin, Raymond, 1947, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 263)
  - Jewish National and University Library, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 263)
  - Johns, Doris C., 1951 (Box 11, Folder 263)
  - Jones, Gordon W., 1952 (Box 11, Folder 263)
  - Jones, Thomas B., 1950-1951, 1957-1962 (Box 11, Folder 264)
  - Jordan, Department of Antiquities, undated (Box 11, Folder 264)
  - Journal of Biblical Literature, 1951, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 264)
    See also: box 8, folder 186
  - Journal of Cuneiform Studies, 1946-1968, undated (Box 11, Folder 265)
    See also: box 11, folder 252 See also: box 17, folder 446-451
  - Journal of Jewish Bibliography, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 266)
  - Journal of Near Eastern Studies, 1938-1953 (Box 11, Folder 266)
  - Journal of the American Oriental Society, 1936-1939, 1950, 1957-1968 (Box 11, Folder 267)
    See also: box 4, folder 103
  - Jucquois, Guy, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 268)
  - Junker, Heinrich, 1924-1928 (Box 11, Folder 268)
  - Kahle, Paul, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 269)
  - Kalantar, Aškharbek, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 269)
  - Kammenhuber, Annalies(*), 1939, 1954-1971 (Box 11, Folder 269)
  - Kampman, A.A., 1936, 1945-1946, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 270)
  - Kansas City, Nelson Gallery of Art, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 270)
  - Kantor, Helene J., 1948, 1957-1964 (Box 11, Folder 270)
  - Kapelrud, Arvid S., 1950-1960 (Box 11, Folder 271)
  - Karstien, Carl, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 271)
  - Kastberger, Francis, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 271)
  - Katsh, Abraham, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 271)
  - Katz, Ilse (Mrs. W.), 1944 (Box 11, Folder 271)
  - Kaye, Alan S., 1965, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 272)
  - Kayser, Stefan, 1938, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 272)
  - Keen, Florence, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 272)
  - Kees, Hermann A.J., 1928, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 272)
  - Kellogg, Robert, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 272)
  - Kelly, M.N., 1964 (Box 11, Folder 272)
  - Kelso de Montigny, Alan H., 1946 (Box 11, Folder 272)
  - Kempner, Robert M.W., 1952 (Box 11, Folder 272)
    See also: box 8, folder 200
  - Kennedy, Douglas A., 1957-1960 (Box 11, Folder 272)
  - Kennedy, E.S., 1952 (Box 11, Folder 273)
  - Kennedy, G.M. (Mrs. Fred), 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 273)
  - Kennedy, George A., 1937 (Box 11, Folder 273)
  - Kennedy, Myron, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 273)
  - [Kenrick?], F.W., 1926 (Box 11, Folder 273)
  - Kent, Roland G.(*), 1945-1951 (Box 11, Folder 274)
  - Kentucky, University of, Foreign Language Conference, 1951-1957 (Box 11, Folder 275)
  - Kenyon, Arthur F., 1964 (Box 11, Folder 275)
  - Kepke, John, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 276)
  - Khayats Publishers, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 276)
  - Kienast, Burkhart, 1956-1965, undated (Box 11, Folder 276)
  - Kilmer, Anne D.(*), 1958-1959, 1964-1968 (Box 11, Folder 277)
  - Kinal, Furrizan, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 277)
  - Kinay, Çahit, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 277)
  - King, Marian, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 278)
  - Kinnier Wilson, J.V., 1962 (Box 11, Folder 278)
  - Kinsey, Alfred C., 1952 (Box 11, Folder 278)
  - Kizilyay, Hatice, 1951-1952 (Box 11, Folder 278)
  - Klein, Jacob, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 278)
  - Klengel, Horst, 1965, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 278)
  - Klima, Joseph, 1950-1956, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 279)
  - Knopf, Carl S., 1939-1942 (Box 11, Folder 279)
  - Knudsen, Ebbe E., 1960-1966 (Box 11, Folder 280)
  - Knudstad, Clare, undated (Box 11, Folder 280)
  - Köcher, Franz, 1953-1961 (Box 11, Folder 280)
  - Kölver, Bernhard, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 280)
  - König, Franz W., 1949, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 281)
  - Koerner, Hans Nordhelm von, 1935 (Box 11, Folder 281)
  - Koethe, [Harald?], 1931 (Box 11, Folder 281)
  - Konow, Sten, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 281)
  - Korošec, Viktor, 1929-1930, 1938-1939, 1944-1946 (Box 11, Folder 282)
  - Koschaker, Helene (Mrs. Paul), 1951 (Box 11, Folder 283)
  - Koschaker, Paul(*), 1926, 1930-1935, 1939, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 283)
  - Koschaker, Paul(*), 1947 (Box 12, Folder 284)
  - Koschaker, Paul(*), 1948-1951 (Box 12, Folder 285)
    See also: box 4, folder 87 See also: box 12, folder 301
  - Kraeling, Carl H.(*), 1947-1951 (Box 12, Folder 286)
  - Kraeling, Carl H., 1952-1954 (Box 12, Folder 287-289)
  - Kraeling, Carl H., 1956-1963 (Box 12, Folder 290)
  - Kraeling, Emil G.(*), 1937-1955, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 291)
  - Kraemer, Joel, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 292)
  - Krahe, Hans, 1948-1955 (Box 12, Folder 292)
  - Kramer, Samuel N., 1938-1944 (Box 12, Folder 292)
  - Kramer, Samuel N.(*), 1945-1950 (Box 12, Folder 293)
  - Kramer, Samuel N., 1952-1953, 1957, 1963, undated (Box 12, Folder 294)
  - Kramers, Johannes Hendrik, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 295)
  - Kraus, Fritz R.(*), 1946-1949 (Box 12, Folder 295)
  - Kraus, Fritz R.(*), 1950-1961, undated (Box 12, Folder 296)
  - Krautheimer, Richard, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 297)
  - Kreis, ____, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 297)
  - Kretschmer, Paul, 1925 (Box 12, Folder 297)
  - Kristeller, Paul O., 1935-1939, 1946-1947 (Box 12, Folder 297)
  - Kronasser, Heinz(*), 1955-1963 (Box 12, Folder 297)
  - Kronstein, Heinrich, 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 298)
  - Krückmann, Oluf, 1934-1938 (Box 12, Folder 298)
    See also: box 12, folder 297
  - Krušina-Ğerny, Ladislav J., 1963 (Box 12, Folder 298)
  - Kulling, S., 1960 (Box 12, Folder 298)
  - Kunderewicz, Cezary (Box 12, Folder 298)
  - Kupper, Jean R.(*), 1949-1959, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 298)
  - Kurylowicz, Jerzy, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 299)
  - Kuschke, Arnulf, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 299)
  - Kutscher, [Eduard?] Y [echezkel?], 1961 (Box 12, Folder 299)
  - Kutscher, Raphael, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 299)
  - Kyle, Ralph, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 299)
  - Labat, René(*), 1946-1958 (Box 12, Folder 300)
  - Lacheman, Ernest R.(*), 1937-1949, 1954-1959 (Box 12, Folder 301)
  - Lacour-Gayet, Jacques, 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 302)
  - Ladd, A.T., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 302)
  - Laessøe, Jørgen(*), 1949-1956 (Box 12, Folder 302)
  - Lager, Carl H., 1949 (Box 12, Folder 303)
  - Lager, Helen W. (Mrs. Carl H.), 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 303)
  - Lake, Kirsopp(*), 1938-1940 (Box 12, Folder 303)
  - Lamb, Winifred, 1938, 1940, 1950-1955 (Box 12, Folder 304)
  - Lambdin, Thomas O., 1953 (Box 12, Folder 304)
  - Lambert, William George(*), 1955-1968 (Box 12, Folder 304)
  - Landauer, Walter, 1938-1940 (Box 12, Folder 304)
  - Landsberger, Benno(*), 1923, 1928-1937, 1943-1944, 1947-1958 (Box 12, Folder 305-308)
  - Landsberger, Benno(*), 1959-1965 (Box 12, Folder 305-308)
  - Lane, George S., 1950-1952, 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 310)
  - Langdon, Stephen H., 1931 (Box 12, Folder 310)
  - Language, 1935-1940, 1947, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 310)
    See also: box 3, folder 77 See also: box 9, folder 215
  - Laroche, Emmanuel(*), 1946-1962 (Box 12, Folder 311-312)
  - La Sor, William S., 1952 (Box 13, Folder 313)
  - Lattimore Defense Fund, undated (Box 13, Folder 313)
  - Lautner, Julius G., 1946, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 313)
  - Lawrence College, 1950-1958 (Box 13, Folder 313)
  - Le Breton, Louis, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 313)
  - Lee, D.J.N., 1951-1952, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 313)
  - Leemans, Wilhelm F.(*), 1949, 1956-1966 (Box 13, Folder 314)
  - Lehmann, Karl(*), 1934-1942, 1947-1951 (Box 13, Folder 315)
  - Lehmann, Manfred R. (Box 13, Folder 316)
  - Lehmann, Winfred P.(*), 1942-1964 (Box 13, Folder 316)
  - Lehmann-Hartleben, Karl
    See: box 13, folder 315
  - Lehmann-Haupt, [Ferdinand] F.C.(*), 1924-1935 (Box 13, Folder 317)
  - Leichty, Erle, 1959, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 318)
  - Lenz, Friedrich W., 1947, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 318)
  - Lenzen, Heinrich, 1958-1964 (Box 13, Folder 318)
  - Leschnitzer, Adolf F., 1938-1939 (Box 13, Folder 318)
  - Leslau, Wolf(*), 1943-1953, 1963, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 319)
  - Leumann, Manu, 1922, 1940, 1954-1955, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 319)
  - Levey, Martin, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 320)
  - Levi della Vida, Giorgio, 1938, 1941, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 320)
  - Levine, Baruch, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 320)
  - Levy, Ernst, 1950, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 320)
  - Levy, Selim(*), 1948-1949, 1954-1961 (Box 13, Folder 320)
  - Lewis, Clarence McK., 1949 (Box 13, Folder 320)
  - Lewy, Hildegard (Mrs. Julius)(*), 1938-1950, 1963, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 321)
    See also: box 13, folder 322-325
  - Lewy, Julius(*), 1925-1931 (Box 13, Folder 322-325)
  - Lewy, Julius (Box 13, Folder 326)
  - Lewy, Julius(*), 1933-1934 (Box 13, Folder 327)
  - Lewy, Julius, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 328)
  - Lewy, Julius(*), 1936 (Box 13, Folder 329)
  - Lewy, Julius, 1937-1938 (Box 13, Folder 330-331)
  - Lewy, Julius(*), 1939-1949 (Box 13, Folder 332-334)
  - Lewy, Julius(*), 1953, 1957, 1961-1963, undated (Box 13, Folder 335)
  - Lexikon der Alten Welt, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 335)
  - Lexikon der Frau, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 335)
  - Lichtheim, Miriam, 1947, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 336)
  - Lidzbarski, Mark, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 336)
  - Lieb, Fritz, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 336)
  - Lieberman, Stephen J., 1969 (Box 13, Folder 336)
  - Liebeschütz, Hans, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 336)
  - Lietzmann, Hans, 1925 (Box 13, Folder 336)
  - Life, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 336)
  - Limet, Henri, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 336)
  - Lindhagen, Curt, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 336)
  - Lines, Joan L.
    See: box 14, folder 361
  - Linguistic Institute(*), 1941,1946-1950,1959 (Box 13, Folder 337)
  - Linguistic Society of America(*), 1935-1940, 1946-1969 (Box 13, Folder 338-343)
  - Litke, Richard L., 1954, 1961-1962, 1967. (Box 14, Folder 344)
  - Lloyd, Seton, 1953, 1957, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 345)
  - Loewenstein, Karl, 1934-1937, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 345)
  - Löwi, Moritz, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 345)
  - Lohmann, Johannes, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 345)
  - Loon, Maurits van, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 345)
  - Louvre, Musée du, 1930, 1933, 1946, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 346)
  - Love, ____ (Mrs. R.E.), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 346)
  - Loyalty Committee of Victims of Nazi-Fascist Oppression
  - Luke, Tracy J., 1970 (Box 14, Folder 346)
  - Lutz, Henry F., 1935, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 346)
  - Mabbott, Thomas O., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 347)
  - McCown, Chester Carlton, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 347)
  - McCown, Donald E., 1952-1955 (Box 14, Folder 347)
  - McDonald, William W., 1961 (Box 14, Folder 348)
  - McEwan, Calvin Wells, 1939-1940 (Box 14, Folder 348)
  - McNeill, Ian, 1958, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 348)
  - Magnus-Levy, Adolf, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 349)
  - Malamat, Abraham, 1961, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 349)
  - Mallowan, Max Edgar Lucien, 1948-1952, 1958-1959, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 349)
  - Mansoor, Menahem, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 349)
  - Mantica, Margit, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 349)
  - Mantura, André, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 349)
  - Marburg, Universität (Box 14, Folder 350)
  - Marchand, Hans, [post-1951] (Box 14, Folder 350)
  - Marcus, Ralph(*), 1940-1942, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 351)
  - Marek, Kurt W., 1955 (Box 14, Folder 351)
  - Marstrander, Carl J.S., 1939 (Box 14, Folder 351)
  - Masé, Sadi, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 352)
  - Masson, Olivier, 1950, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 352)
  - Matouš, Lubor(*), 1949-1967 (Box 14, Folder 352)
  - Matthews, Charles D., 1967 (Box 14, Folder 353)
  - Matz, Friedrich, 1931, 1947, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 353)
  - Mayrhofer, Manfred, 1959, 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 353)
  - Mazar, Benjamin, 1962-1966 (Box 14, Folder 353)
  - Meek, Theophile J.(*), 1935-1954, undated (Box 14, Folder 354)
  - Meer, E. van der, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 354)
  - Mehnke, Dietrich, 1933-1934 (Box 14, Folder 354)
  - Meier, H[arri?], 1936 (Box 14, Folder 354)
  - Meissner, Bruno, 1924-1933 (Box 14, Folder 355)
  - Mélanges Boisacq, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 355)
  - Mellart, James, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 355)
  - Mellink, Machteld(*), 1950-1961, 1963-1971 (Box 14, Folder 356-358)
  - Mendelsohn, Isaac, 1946, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 359)
  - Menges, Karl H., 1941-1943, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 359)
  - Mercer, Samuel A.B., 1924, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 359)
  - Merhart von Bernegg, Gero, 1932-1935, 1946, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 359)
  - Meriggi, Piero(*), 1928-1938, 1948-1955, 1963-1970 (Box 14, Folder 360)
  - Mescaninov, I., 1946 (Box 14, Folder 361)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1935, 1947, 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 361)
    See also: box 20, folder 538
  - Meyer, Gerhard Rudolf, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 361)
  - Mezger, F., 1943-1951 (Box 14, Folder 361)
  - Michigan, University of, Kelsey Museum of Archaeology, 1945, 1953, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 361)
  - Miles, John, 1949-1956 (Box 14, Folder 362)
  - Milgrom, Jacob, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 362)
  - Miller, Madeleine S. (Mrs. J. Lane), 1947-1949 (Box 14, Folder 362)
  - Mittelberger, H., 1965 (Box 14, Folder 363)
  - Moberg, Axel, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 363)
  - Modi, Jivanji J., 1924-1929 (Box 14, Folder 363)
  - Möbius, Hans, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 363)
  - Moller, ____ (of Copenhagen), 1935 (Box 14, Folder 363)
  - Montgomery, James A., 1938 (Box 14, Folder 363)
  - Montgomery, James A., Jr., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 363)
  - Moortgat, Anton, 1932, 1951, 1957, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 363)
  - Moortgat-Correns, Ursula, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 363)
    See also: box 4, folder 81 See also: box 17, folder 420-422
  - Moran, William L.(*), 1950-1953, 1962-1967 (Box 14, Folder 364)
  - Moreau-Neret, H. (Mrs.), 1964 (Box 14, Folder 365)
  - Morgan, Walter L., 1949 (Box 14, Folder 365)
  - Morgenstern, Julian, 1936, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 365)
  - Morgenstierne, Georg, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 365)
  - Morrison, Ellen E., 1970 (Box 14, Folder 365)
  - Morrison, Orville C., 1963 (Box 14, Folder 365)
  - Moscati, Sabatino, 1954, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 366)
  - Mossner, Friedrich, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 366)
  - Mouterde, René, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 366)
  - Mowry, Lucetta, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 366)
  - Müller, Manfred, 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 366)
  - Müller, Valentin, 1925-1930 (Box 14, Folder 366)
  - Muhly, James D., 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 366)
  - Muilenburg, James, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 367)
  - Munscher, Karl, 1925, 1927 (Box 14, Folder 367)
  - Murray, D.F., 1958 (Box 14, Folder 367)
  - Must, Gustav, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 367)
  - Myres, John L., 1934 (Box 14, Folder 367)
  - Nagel, Wolfram, 1957-1961 (Box 14, Folder 368)
    See also: box 20, folder 514
  - Nalbandian, V. Calantar, 1936-1946 (Box 14, Folder 368)
  - Nalbandian, V. Calantar(*), 1965 (Box 14, Folder 369)
  - Nandris, Octave, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 369)
  - Naster, Paul, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 369)
  - National Council of the Churches of Christ
    See: box 20, folder 522
  - National Science Foundation, 1960-1962 (Box 14, Folder 369)
  - Naumann, Hanna(Mrs. Walter)
    See: box 11, folder 257
  - Naumann, Rudolf, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 369)
  - Naumann, Walter(*), 1937-1938 (Box 14, Folder 370)
  - Naumann, Walter(*), 1939-1943, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 371)
  - Nebraska State Museum, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 371)
  - Neely, Dan, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 371)
  - Nehring, Alfons, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 371)
  - Nemirovskij, Mikhail I., 1930-1931 (Box 14, Folder 372)
  - Nestman, Caroline, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 372)
  - Neufeld, Ephraim(*), 1945-1952 (Box 14, Folder 372)
  - Neugebauer, Otto(*), 1929-1954 (Box 15, Folder 373-379)
  - Neugebauer, Otto(*), 1955-1961, 1968-1970, undated (Box 15, Folder 380)
    See also: box 5, folder 118
  - Neumann, Günther, 1958-1965 (Box 15, Folder 381)
  - New Schaff-Herzog Encyclopedia of Religous Knowledge, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 381)
  - Nibli, Sandra, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 381)
  - Nilsson, Martin, 1934 (Box 15, Folder 381)
  - Nippur, Joint Expedition to
  - Nobel, Johannes(*), 1935, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 381)
  - Nobel, Johannes, 1947-1949 (Box 15, Folder 382)
  - Nobel Komittee der Schweischen Academie, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 382)
  - Nock, Arthur D., 1938 (Box 15, Folder 382)
  - Nökleke, Theodor, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 382)
  - North Carolina, University of, Library, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 382)
  - Notgemeinschaft Deutscher Wissenschaftler im Ausland, 1934-1939, undated (Box 15, Folder 383)
  - Noth, Martin, 1953-1963 (Box 15, Folder 384)
  - Nougayrol, Jean(*), 1945-1971 (Box 15, Folder 385-387)
  - Nyberg, Henrik S.(*), 1937, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 388)
  - Oates, David, 1963, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 388)
  - Oates, Joan (Mrs. David), 1957-1965 (Box 15, Folder 388)
  - Obermann, Julian J., 1935-1939, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 388)
  - O'Callaghan, Roger T., 1947-1953 (Box 16, Folder 389)
  - O'Callahan, John H., 1954-1955 (Box 16, Folder 389)
  - Odewald, Max, 1940-1941 (Box 16, Folder 389)
  - Oelsner, Joachim, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 389)
  - Özgüç, Nimet (Mrs. Tahsin), 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 390)
  - Özgüç, Tahsin, 1950-1955, 1961-1963 (Box 16, Folder 390)
  - Ogan, Aziz
    See: box 11, folder 251
  - O'Halloran, John L., 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 391)
  - Oklahoma, University of, Stovall Museum of Science and History, 1954-1962 (Box 16, Folder 391)
  - Old Lyme High School, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 391)
  - Oliver, Harry, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 391)
  - Olmstead, Albert Ten Eyck, 1927-1929, 1936 (Box 16, Folder 391)
  - Oney, Ernest R., 1951 (Box 16, Folder 391)
  - Opificius, Peter, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 391)
  - Oppenheim, A. Leo(*), 1933-1921, undated (Box 16, Folder 392-393)
  - Oppenheim, A. Leo(*), 1952-1960, undated (Box 16, Folder 394)
    See also: box 6, folder 147-152
  - Oppenheim, Max Freiherr von(*), 1930-1937 (Box 16, Folder 395)
  - Orientalia, 1962-1965 (Box 16, Folder 395)
  - Orlinsky, Harry M., 1955 (Box 16, Folder 395)
  - Osgood, Cornelius, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 396)
  - Osten, Hans Henning von der, 1929-1931, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 396)
  - Ostern, Hermann, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 397)
  - Ostrowski, ____, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 397)
  - Ott, Lawrence, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 397)
  - Otten, Heinrich(*), 1946-1958, 1961-1971 (Box 16, Folder 398-400)
  - Otto, Walter [G.A.?](*), 1924-1932 (Box 16, Folder 401)
  - Owen, David I., undated (Box 16, Folder 401)
  - Owens, Thomas R., 1947 (Box 16, Folder 402)
  - "Owl"
    See: box 17, folder 446-451
  - Page, Stephanie, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 402)
  - Palestine, Department of Antiquities, 1928 (Box 16, Folder 402)
  - Palmer, Charles L., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 403)
  - Palmer, Leonard Robert, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 403)
  - Panofsky, Erwin, 1936, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 403)
  - Paper, Herbert H., 1950-1954 (Box 16, Folder 403)
  - Parker, Barbara, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 404)
  - Parker, Richard A., 1955 (Box 16, Folder 404)
  - Parrot, André, 1946, 1951, 1959-1966 (Box 16, Folder 404)
  - Pasquali, Giorgio, 1927 (Box 16, Folder 404)
  - Paulyschen Realenzyklopädie, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 404)
  - Pavry, Jal Dastur C., 1929 (Box 16, Folder 404)
  - Pawlikowski-Cholewa, Alfred von, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 404)
  - Pearlman, Raymond, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 405)
  - Peck, Caroline (Mrs. Russell A., Jr.), 1954 (Box 16, Folder 405)
  - Pedersen, Holger(*), 1933-1940, 1946-1953 (Box 16, Folder 405)
  - Pedersen, Johannes, 1945, 1951-1957 (Box 16, Folder 406)
  - Peet, Thomas E., 1928 (Box 16, Folder 406)
  - Pennsylvania, University of, Department of Oriental Studies, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 407)
  - Pennsylvania, University of, Museum, 1935-1951, undated (Box 16, Folder 407)
    See also: box 5, folder 115
  - Perkins, ____, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 407)
  - Perry, B.E., 1945 (Box 16, Folder 407)
  - Persson, Per, 1935 (Box 16, Folder 407)
  - Peruzzi, Emilio, 1948, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 407)
  - Petersen, Walter, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 408)
  - Petschow, Herbert, 1955-1966 (Box 16, Folder 408)
  - Peyre, Henri, 1951, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 408)
  - Pfeiffer, Robert H.(*), 1935-1938 (Box 16, Folder 409)
  - Pfeiffer, Robert H.(*), 1940-1954 (Box 16, Folder 410)
    See also: box 20, folder 528
  - Pfeufer, James F., 1964 (Box 16, Folder 411)
  - Phillips, Clifford H., 1936 (Box 16, Folder 411)
  - Piankoff, Alexander, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 411)
  - Pierce, Robert M., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 411)